{
    "subject": "resource/Anne_Sjerp_Troelstra",
    "predicate": "ontology/doctoralStudent",
    "object": "resource/Ieke_Moerdijk",
    "human_readable": "Anne Sjerp Troelstra was a doctoral student of Ieke Moerdijk.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9835823774337769,
            "question": "Who was Anne Sjerp Troelstra a doctoral student of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9725525379180908,
            "question": "Was Anne Sjerp Troelstra a student?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9398078322410583,
            "question": "Could Anne Sjerp Troelstra have learned from Ieke Moerdijk?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9252935647964478,
            "question": "In what field of study might Anne Sjerp Troelstra and Ieke Moerdijk have worked?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8592649102210999,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Anne Sjerp Troelstra and Ieke Moerdijk?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7712555527687073,
            "question": "Who was Ieke Moerdijk?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7701534032821655,
            "question": "Do you know of any publications by Anne Sjerp Troelstra or Ieke Moerdijk?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20236141979694366,
            "question": "What is a doctorate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19596223533153534,
            "question": "What might be some common research interests between a doctoral student and their advisor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09740003943443298,
            "question": "Can you think of other examples of student-teacher relationships in academia?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Anne Sjerp Troelstra was a doctoral student of Ieke Moerdijk.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7586_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might be some common research interests between a doctoral student and their advisor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7586_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is a doctorate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7586_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know of any publications by Anne Sjerp Troelstra or Ieke Moerdijk?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7586_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7586_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7586_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7586_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7586_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7586_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7586_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7586_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7586_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7586_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7586_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that there is no mention of Anne Sjerp Troelstra being a doctoral student of Ieke Moerdijk in any of the provided documents. The documents only mention his relationship with Arend Heyting and other mathematicians, but not Ieke Moerdijk."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not mention Anne Sjerp Troelstra being a doctoral student of Ieke Moerdijk. Instead, the information indicates that he was advised by Arend Heyting and had students such as Olga Bakker and E.W. Beth's students Dick de Jongh and Hans Kamp."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information in the context provided suggesting that Anne Sjerp Troelstra was a doctoral student of Ieke Moerdijk.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "He was advised by Arend Heyting as his advisor.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Ieke Moerdijk as Anne Sjerp Troelstra's supervisor or advisor, and the context suggests that Arend Heyting was his advisor.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information mentions Anne Sjerp Troelstra as a professor of pure mathematics and foundations of mathematics, advising students like Olga Bakker and having connections with other mathematicians such as Dirk van Dalen and Henk Barendregt. There is no mention of Ieke Moerdijk being his doctoral student or any indication that Troelstra was supervised by Moerdijk during his studies.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}